corporate-ir.net 2004-12-05

# CCBN's Privacy Policy

| 

Your privacy, and the privacy of all registered users of the services of CCBN.com, is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of personally-identifiable information regarding our users and their activities at our site. This policy applies to all visitors to [www.ccbn.com](http://www.ccbn.com/), [www.companyboardroom.com](http://www.companyboardroom.com/), and all registered users of [www.streetevents.com](http://www.streetevents.com/) and [my.ccbn.com](http://my.ccbn.com/).

1\. Notice

This policy tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at [info@ccbn.com](mailto:info@ccbn.com?subject=privacy%20policy) if you have any questions regarding its contents.

Types of Information Collected  
In connection with your use of our site, we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in different ways. For example, when you register to use our site, we ask for and store your and/or your business’ name, address, e-mail address and other identifying contact data. We may also receive information about you through the Web sites of the companies for which we provide investor relations services.

Use of Cookies  
Use of our registered user areas requires that you accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that our Web site sends to your browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at our site and better serve your needs and interests.

Use of Information  
We use your personally identifying information to identify you as a user of the site and to allow you access to the registered user sections of the site. We may use your e-mail address to contact you directly regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site and other transactions you effect through the site. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the site based on your preferences and activities.

We may combine your personally identifying information, and information about your preferences and activities, with those of all or a particular group of our users to prepare collective profiles of our users and their activities. For example, we may track the number of our users who view certain pages, [or] use certain features or compile the total number of visitors to our site in a particular geographic region. Such information, and other information we derive from individual users’ information, allows us to continue to grow and provide you with quality services, as well as develop more accurate marketing and advertising for our Web site.

Disclosure of Information  
We do not release your personally identifying information, and information about your activities and preferences, to other companies wishing to contact you about products or services. We may, however, provide third parties with collective profiles of our user groups and their activities and preferences. Such collective profiles may also be disclosed in describing our site and services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

Your information may be provided to the company for which we are under contract to provide investor relations services to you. Such information will be handled in accordance with that company’s privacy policies. However, we do not disclose information about a company’s investors to the other companies for which we provide investor relations services.

Finally, we may disclose information as necessary to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements; to effect a sale, assignment, or other transfer of our assets or one or more of our service agreements; or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others’ rights or to prevent harm.

2\. Choice

You may choose to restrict our use of your information to maintaining your registration on the site, or prohibit our disclosure of your information to others, by contacting us and directing us to impose such limits. If you wish us to restrict the use or disclosure of your information, please send us an e-mail at [info@ccbn.com](mailto:info@ccbn.com?subject=privacy%20policy). Since we must use and disclose certain information in order provide services to you, your decision to opt out may mean that you can no longer receive some or all of the services we offer.

In addition, we will not send unsolicited messages to users of our site who indicate that they do not wish to receive such messages. If you do not wish to receive unsolicited e-mail messages from us, please contact us at [info@ccbn.com](mailto:info@ccbn.com?subject=privacy%20policy).

3\. Access

At any time after you have logged on to our site, you may contact us at [info@ccbn.com](mailto:info@ccbn.com?subject=privacy%20policy) to request access to information we have collected regarding you or your business or to notify us of changes to such information. You may also contact us by mail at Attn: Data Access, 343 Congress Street, Boston, MA 02210, by telephone at 617.603.7900, or by facsimile at 617.603.7800. If you request any changes, we will contact you by e-mail or fax to confirm those changes. Once confirmed, any new item of information will replace the corresponding information previously provided.

4\. Control of Your Password

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password, including fees. Therefore, we recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password as detailed in the profiles page of the product for which you are registered.

5\. Security

We use industry-standard encryption methods to transmit your personal registration information from your computer to ours across the Internet, and we restrict access to any registered user portions of our site to computers running web browsers that support Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. To use this protection technology, you need to have an SSL-compatible browser. These browsers will automatically activate the technology when you log on to our site. We use industry standard practices to insure your personally identifiable information is secure, including firewalls.

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our site should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. And, after you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information. Remember that any information you voluntarily disclose on-line in any news or message postings, discussion groups or chat rooms may be collected and used by others without your permission. Furthermore, if you provide any information to parties who operate Web sites that are linked to or from our site, different rules may apply to their collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to review these sites’ policies before revealing any sensitive or personal information.

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time without prior notice. Revisions will be posted on our Web sites. This Privacy Policy is for the information of our users and does not constitute a contract or modification of any contract.

|
